

# **HAFIDH SYAHPUTRA**

089667887044 | hafidhsyahputra99@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hafidh-syahputra/ | https://hast99.github.io/

Salakan No. 103 RT. 04

I have more than three years experience in quality assurance. Accustomed to generating Test Case scenarios and locating faults in the website and API. I highly motivated to develop my skills and learn more about quality assurance in order to become a professional quality assurance.

## **Work Experiences**

### PT. Cerdas Digital Nusantara (CAKAP) - Sleman, D.I

Aug 2020 - Dec 2022

Yogyakarta

Quality Assurance

- · Manual testing of the functionality and usability of mobile apps and web apps in staging and beta phases
- · Create a bug discovery report and use Jira
- · Having knowledge about REST API testing Postman
- · Understand the testing stages in SDLC
- · Familiar with Agile frameworks scrum

#### PT. Erporate Solusi Global - Sleman, D.I Yogyakarta

Jul 2019 - Jun 2020

Quality Assurance

- · Create a bug discovery report and use Trello and Google Docs to collaborate with each other.
- Manual testing of the functionality and usability of mobile apps and web apps in staging and beta phases.

#### Dokter PC - Yogyakarta, D.I Yogyakarta

Mar 2017 - Jun 2018

Technician

- · Repair software & hardware
- · Install the operating system

#### **Education Level**

## Universitas Teknologi Digital Indonesia - Bantul, D.I Yogyakarta

Sep 2020 - Mar 2023 (Expected)

Bachelor Degree in Informatics, 3.70/4.00

SMK Muhammadiyah 1 Yogyakarta - Yogyakarta, D.I Yogyakarta

Apr 2014 - May 2017

Computer Network Enginnering

#### Organisational Experience

#### Informatics and computers UKM - Bantul, D.I Yogyakarta

Aug 2021 - Present

Division coordinator

Salakan Youth Organization - Bantul, D.I Yogyakarta

Apr 2019 - Jun 2022

Leader

## **Skills & Other Experience**

- Soft Skills: Communication, Teamwork, Problem solving, Creative Thinking, Time Management, Analytical and Strategic Thinking.
- Hard Skills: HTML, CSS: TailwindCSS, Basic Java, Angular, Basic PHP, Java (Spring), MVC, Git, MySQL, REST APIs, Postman, Jira, Adobe Photoshop, Canva, Figma
- Interest: Photographer & Videographer